

ANTHONY GREELEY

Chicago, IL 💡

(847)848-0552

tony.greeley@me.com

github.com/tonythetiger323 🖸

tonygreeley.dev 😵

JUNIOR FULL STACK REACT DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated individual seeking employment with a company that values their employees skills as well as embraces their individuality. Looking to become a React developer, in particular back end software development, as it is a key strength of mine and is where I hope my career takes me. Having worked in tech support for various companies over the past 13 years has given me a foundation for it. Problem solving with creative solutions has proven to be a valuable skill to help me excel in software development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2U, INC. PRII 2020 -

APRIL 2020 -PRESENT

Teacher's Assistant

Substitute assistant until September when I was assigned a permanent spot in September for the full-stack web development coding boot camp held at Northwestern University. Assist instructor in managing class time management, helping students in learning, and completing homework assignments using a lead learning out approach, guiding them to solutions by asking open-ended questions, helping manage the grade book, encouraging/supporting students throughout the course, and acting as a liaison between students and student success manager if needed, other administrative tasks such as managing attendance.

APPLE, INC.

JULY 2010 -

SEPT 2019

Genius

Repaired customer relationships with Apple by being efficient in building rapport with customers, through mac and mobile hardware repair, as well as using creative thinking for macOS/iOS/watchOS/tvOS software troubleshooting. In addition also at times facilitated training for new hires, and helped develop peers by providing feedback.

VERIZON WIRELESS

2006 - 2010

Retail Sales Representative/Data Champion

Determine customers wireless needs and create custom solutions to meet them. Taught monthly advanced device workshops for customer as well as coaching and developing peer in offering various data services to customers.

CINGULAR WIRELESS

2000 - 2006

Retail Sales Consultant/Acting Manager

In addition to helping customer's with their wireless needs, was responsible for ordering, receiving, and reconciling store inventory; scheduling and payroll, resolving customer employee conflict, planning/preparing weekly store meetings, and other advanced administrative roles.

EDUCATION

NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY

AUGUST 2018 -MARCH 2019

Web Development Certificate

Full-stack web development utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and the MERN (Mongo, Express, React, Node) stack.

COLORADO TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY ONLINE

Associate of Science in Business Administration

Business fundamentals and administration techniques.

MARCH 2007 -APRIL 2008